let savollar5 = [
    {
      numb: 1,
      question: "to acquaint",
      answer: "C. tanishmoq",
      options: [
        "A. unutmoq",
        "B. e'tiborsiz qoldirmoq",
        "C. tanishmoq",
        "D. olib tashlamoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 2,
      question: "cemetery",
      answer: "B. qabriston",
      options: [
        "A. bog'",
        "B. qabriston",
        "C. maydon",
        "D. masjid"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 3,
      question: "to curse",
      answer: "D. la'natlamoq",
      options: [
        "A. duo qilmoq",
        "B. hurmat qilmoq",
        "C. ko'rsatmoq",
        "D. la'natlamoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 4,
      question: "disguise",
      answer: "A. niqob",
      options: [
        "A. niqob",
        "B. kiyim",
        "C. qalqon",
        "D. qurol"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 5,
      question: "fancy",
      answer: "C. chiroyli",
      options: [
        "A. oddiy",
        "B. toza",
        "C. chiroyli",
        "D. eski"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 6,
      question: "flashlight",
      answer: "B. fonar",
      options: [
        "A. sham",
        "B. fonar",
        "C. lampa",
        "D. oyna"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 7,
      question: "hood",
      answer: "D. kapyushon",
      options: [
        "A. sharf",
        "B. shlyapa",
        "C. ko'ylak",
        "D. kapyushon"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 8,
      question: "inhabitant",
      answer: "B. istiqomat qiluvchi",
      options: [
        "A. mehmon",
        "B. istiqomat qiluvchi",
        "C. sayohatchi",
        "D. xorijlik"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 9,
      question: "to nourish",
      answer: "A. boqmoq",
      options: [
        "A. boqmoq",
        "B. unutmok",
        "C. oziq yetkazmaslik",
        "D. bekor qilish"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 10,
      question: "pirate",
      answer: "C. qaroqchi",
      options: [
        "A. dengizchi",
        "B. sotuvchi",
        "C. qaroqchi",
        "D. kapitan"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 11,
      question: "publication",
      answer: "B. nashr",
      options: [
        "A. qo'lyozma",
        "B. nashr",
        "C. maqola",
        "D. sxema"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 12,
      question: "riddle",
      answer: "C. topishmoq",
      options: [
        "A. savol",
        "B. hazil",
        "C. topishmoq",
        "D. masala"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 13,
      question: "to rot",
      answer: "B. chirimoq",
      options: [
        "A. ko'karmoq",
        "B. chirimoq",
        "C. o'smoq",
        "D. qurimoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 14,
      question: "to scare",
      answer: "C. qo'rqitmoq",
      options: [
        "A. tinchlantirmoq",
        "B. quvontirmoq",
        "C. qo'rqitmoq",
        "D. zeriktirmoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 15,
      question: "shortly",
      answer: "A. tez orada",
      options: [
        "A. tez orada",
        "B. hech qachon",
        "C. juda uzoq",
        "D. doimiy"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 16,
      question: "skeleton",
      answer: "D. skelet",
      options: [
        "A. suyaklar",
        "B. haykal",
        "C. shisha",
        "D. skelet"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 17,
      question: "to spoil",
      answer: "C. aynimoq",
      options: [
        "A. yaxshilamoq",
        "B. saqlamoq",
        "C. aynimoq",
        "D. yaxshilash"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 18,
      question: "to starve",
      answer: "B. och qolmoq",
      options: [
        "A. to'yib ovqatlanmoq",
        "B. och qolmoq",
        "C. rohatlanmoq",
        "D. tinchlanmoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 19,
      question: "thrill",
      answer: "A. hayajon",
      options: [
        "A. hayajon",
        "B. qo'rquv",
        "C. mazza",
        "D. tinchlik"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 20,
      question: "wicked",
      answer: "D. yovuz",
      options: [
        "A. yaxshi",
        "B. mehribon",
        "C. aqlli",
        "D. yovuz"
      ]
    }
  ];
  
  export default savollar5;
  